goldennugget.com 2017-06-17

# Golden Nugget Las Vegas | Privacy Policy

**I. APPLICATION OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
**   
This Privacy Policy applies to all web sites owned or operated by Fertitta Entertainment, Inc., Landry’s Holdings, Inc., Fertitta Group, Inc., Landry’s Inc., Golden Nugget, Inc., GNLV Corp., and their respective parents, subsidiaries, and affiliates (one or more such entities being referred to herein as “Golden Nugget”), including, but not limited to, the web sites for: (1) Golden Nugget at goldennugget.com, and (2) goldennuggetpoker.com, together with any computer applications downloaded there from (collectively, “Golden Nugget Web Sites”). Golden Nugget Web Sites may be accessed through domain names in addition to the domain names listed above. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by Golden Nugget by means other than through Golden Nugget Web Sites.

Certain transactions and services offered while visiting Golden Nugget Web Sites may be processed or provided by strategic partners under contract with Golden Nugget, even though it appears that you may not have left the Golden Nugget web site (collectively, "Strategic Partners").

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by Strategic Partners, except that Golden Nugget will treat information it receives about you from Strategic Partners under the terms of this Privacy Policy. Golden Nugget does not have any control over how Strategic Partners use information they collect about you. To determine the privacy policy applicable to information collected by these Strategic Partners, please consult the web sites of the Strategic Partners.  

**II. INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU  
**General Information  
When you use the Internet, your web browser or client software may transmit certain information to the servers that host the web sites you visit. The information may include (1) IP address, (2) domain server, (3) type of computer, (4) type of web browser, (5) the capabilities and features of your computer, (6) your geographic location, and (6) your movement within and interaction with the web site, including what pages you look at and what information you download (collectively, “Traffic Data”). When you visit Golden Nugget Web Sites, Golden Nugget servers collect Traffic Data and Golden Nugget uses this information to generate aggregate statistics about visitors to Golden Nugget Web Sites for marketing purposes and to improve your experience on Golden Nugget Web Sites.

Personally Identifying Information  
Golden Nugget only collects personal information that you voluntarily provide to us or voluntarily provide to Strategic Partners who share that information with us. "Personal Information" is information through which you can be identified. The Personal Information that Golden Nugget collects through Golden Nugget Web Sites or obtains from its Strategic Partners depends on the nature of your online activity, such as whether you make reservations, sign the guestbook, play games, plan a meeting, purchase show tickets or merchandise, or complete a casino patron application. Personal Information that Golden Nugget may collect from you directly or through Strategic Partners, includes your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number(s), fax number, birth date, gender, credit card or bank account information, purchase and reservation information, gaming activity, and other information that you voluntarily provide. When you complete a casino patron or online player application, Golden Nugget may also collect the name of your firm or employer, your firm's or employer’s address and telephone number, your position with the firm or employer, your social security number, banking information (including the name and address of your primary and secondary banks and your account numbers) and other credit information. The Personal Information is collected by e-mail, through online forms, and through your activities on Golden Nugget Web Sites.

Cookies  
Golden Nugget Web Sites use cookie technology. A cookie is a small file that contains information sent by a web site that is saved on your hard disk by your computer's browser. Cookies store information that a web site may need to personalize your experience and to gather web site statistical data, such as which pages you visit, what material you download, your internet provider's domain name and country, and the addresses of web sites you visited immediately before, and after, visiting a particular web site.

Golden Nugget Web Sites use cookies to collect and store your preferences for viewing the Golden Nugget Web Sites, such as whether you disable Flash so that you will not have to do so on follow up visits. In addition, Golden Nugget Web Sites use cookies to provide a unique identifier to your computer so that we can generate statistics regarding usage of Golden Nugget Web Sites, such as the percentage of repeat visitors and other general statistics. The unique identifiers are not matched with any personal information. In addition, when you book a reservation online to stay at a Golden Nugget property, the reservation or confirmation number may be stored in a cookie on your computer. Moreover, cookies used by Golden Nugget Web Sites do not store any Personal Information about you.

To browse the Internet and Golden Nugget Web Sites without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies or to notify you when each cookie is offered so that you can accept or reject each cookie. You may not be able to conduct some transactions or use some services on Golden Nugget Web Sites if you disable your browser from accepting cookies.  

**III. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
**Golden Nugget may use the information collected by us or Strategic Partners for the following reasons: (1) for marketing purposes, including, but not limited to, notifying you of special promotions, offers and events by Golden Nugget and/or its affiliates or other associated third parties; (2) to process and fulfill reservations and make a record of reservations; (3) to process and fulfill purchases and make a record of purchases, prizes, or rewards; (4) to enable us to contact you for confirmation or customer service after reservations and purchases are made or after you sign up for or participate in certain activities; (5) to respond to inquiries, complaints and other communications; (6) to cross-reference with other Personal Information that we have acquired about you or may acquire about you through other sources; (7) for profiling or demographic purposes; (8) for purposes of tracking reservations and corresponding hotel stays; (9) to be provided to our affiliates or third parties in connection with the legitimate business purposes of Golden Nugget or our Websites; or (10) to protect or defend the rights or property of Golden Nugget or its affiliates or associated third parties.  If you prefer that we not share your nonpublic personal information with third parties, please email us at guestservices@goldennugget.com.   

**IV. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
**Except as provided below, Golden Nugget will not sell, trade, or disclose to third parties any Personal Information obtained through Golden Nugget Web Sites or obtained from Strategic Partners, without your consent. Golden Nugget may disclose Personal Information to (1) parents, subsidiaries and affiliates of Golden Nugget, including owned, operated, and/or managed casinos, hotels, restaurants and other business ventures of Golden Nugget or its parents, subsidiaries and affiliates; (2) Golden Nugget’s business partners for joint marketing efforts, or for such business partners’ own marketing purposes, subject to requiring such business partners to exercise reasonable care to protect Personal information and use such Personal Information only for the purpose for which it was provided to them; (3) in connection with a business reorganization, a merger, change of control, or the sale, assignment, or transfer of any Golden Nugget property or any Golden Nugget Web Site; or (4) to businesses that Golden Nugget may use for purposes of performing functions on behalf of Golden Nugget, including without limitation, companies that process payment transactions or provide credit information.    
Notwithstanding any in this privacy policy to the contrary, Golden Nugget reserves the right to disclose Personal Information when Golden Nugget believes, in its reasonable opinion, that disclosure is necessary: (1) to comply with a court order, subpoena, search warrant or other legal process; (2) to comply with legal, regulatory or administrative requirements of any governmental authorities; (3) to protect and defend Golden Nugget, its subsidiaries and affiliates, and all of their officers, directors, employees, attorneys, agents, contractors, and partners, in connection with any legal action, claim or dispute; (4) to enforce the terms of use of Golden Nugget Web Sites; or (5) to prevent imminent physical harm..  

**V. CHOICE REGARDING PROVIDING INFORMATION  
**General information is collected whenever you browse Golden Nugget Web Sites. The Golden Nugget Web Sites do not provide any means for opting out of providing general information when you browse Golden Nugget Web Sites. However, privacy software that prevents the disclosure of general information is commercially available.

You can browse Golden Nugget Web Sites without providing any Personal Information. However, providing Personal Information is required to use some of the services offered through the Golden Nugget Web Sites, including, but not limited to, making restaurant or hotel reservations, making purchases, and playing games or participating in tournaments, sweepstakes or other prize contests.

You can opt out of receiving certain communications and offers. Opt out options will be indicated when they are available.  

**VI. ACCESS  
**The general or Personal Information collected through Golden Nugget Web Sites or provided by Strategic Partners is not currently accessible to you, except that confirmation is provided for some transactions and services, such as reservations and purchases. If you believe that any information collected by Golden Nugget about you is not correct or has changed, please send an e-mail message to guestservices@goldennugget.com explaining the correction or change and provide any relevant confirmation or reference number.  

**VII. SECURITY  
**We use reasonable security safeguards to protect the Personal Information that we collect from unauthorized access. However, due to the design of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and our servers will be free from unauthorized access by third parties.  
We cannot enforce or control the security of the computers, electronic devices, or electronic communication methods that you may use to send emails and submit information to Golden Nugget over the internet.  You are responsible for ensuring that the computers, electronic devices and electronic communication methods you use will provide adequate security for communicating with Golden Nugget.  Golden Nugget is not responsible for the disclosure or interception of information that you send before Golden Nugget receives it.  

**VIII. AGE RESTRICTIONS AND THE CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT  
**Pursuant to law, persons under the age of twenty-one (21) are not permitted to participate in online gaming or gamble in casinos and are not permitted to loiter in the gaming areas of any Golden Nugget properties. Similarly, Golden Nugget Web Sites are general audience sites intended only for persons 21 years of age or older. Golden Nugget has no intention of collecting any personally identifiable information (name address, telephone number, birth date, or email address) from individuals under 21 years of age.  Accordingly, the provisions of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act do not apply to Golden Nugget Web Sites.  If a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, a parent or guardian of that child can contact us at the e-mail address or phone number listed in the Contact Us section of the website if they would like this information deleted from our records. We will use reasonable efforts to delete the child’s information from our existing records. For more information about protecting the privacy and safety of minors online, we recommend you visit http://onguardonline.gov/articles/0031-kids%E2%80%99-privacy.   

**IX. NON-U.S. RESIDENTS  
**Unless otherwise specified, this Site and material provided on this Site are solely for promoting products, programs, and business operations within the U.S. If you do not reside in the U.S. and are visiting this Site, if you provide Personal Information to us, it may be transferred to and processed on computers in the U.S. and other countries. Do not provide your Personal Information to us if you do not want this information to be transferred outside of your country, or if the laws in your country restrict these types of transfers. Instead, please contact us guestservices@goldennugget.com. Your provision of Personal Information to us will be handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Your provision of Personal Information to us through this Site means that you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  

**X. CHANGES  
**This Privacy Policy was posted on June 5, 2012. Golden Nugget reserves the right to change, modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. When the Privacy Policy is changed, modified and/or amended, the revised Privacy Policy will be posted on Golden Nugget Web Sites. Any revised Privacy Policy will only apply prospectively to Personal Information collected or modified after the effective date of the revised policy. Customers are responsible for periodically checking the Privacy Policy posted on Golden Nugget Web Sites for changes.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at guestservices@goldennugget.com
